{
    "questions": [
        {
            "answer": "c",
            "img_src": "",
            "options": [
                "American",
                "Australian",
                "Japanese",
                "Malaysian"
            ],
            "question": "Which nationality is associated with sushi and cherry blossoms?",
            "type": "multiple_choice"
        },
        {
            "answer": "c",
            "img_src": "",
            "options": [
                "American",
                "British",
                "Indian",
                "Chinese"
            ],
            "question": "If someone is from India, their nationality is...",
            "type": "multiple_choice"
        },
        {
            "answer": "d",
            "img_src": "",
            "options": [
                "Malaysian",
                "Japanese",
                "British",
                "Chinese"
            ],
            "question": "A person from China is called a...",
            "type": "multiple_choice"
        },
        {
            "answer": "b",
            "img_src": "",
            "options": [
                "Clever",
                "Helpful",
                "Active",
                "Appearance"
            ],
            "question": "What word describes a person who is always willing to assist others?",
            "type": "multiple_choice"
        },
        {
            "answer": "a",
            "img_src": "",
            "options": [
                "Friendly",
                "Shy",
                "Clever",
                "Nationality"
            ],
            "question": "Which of the following best describes a person who enjoys socializing and easily meets new people?",
            "type": "multiple_choice"
        },
        {
            "answer": "c",
            "img_src": "",
            "options": [
                "Personality",
                "Clever",
                "Appearance",
                "Invite"
            ],
            "question": "What is the word for how someone looks, including their height, hair, and face?",
            "type": "multiple_choice"
        },
        {
            "answer": "a",
            "img_src": "",
            "options": [
                "Invite",
                "Make friends",
                "Help",
                "Active"
            ],
            "question": "If you ask someone to come to your birthday party, you... them.",
            "type": "multiple_choice"
        },
        {
            "answer": "c",
            "img_src": "",
            "options": [
                "Friendly",
                "Active",
                "Clever",
                "Helpful"
            ],
            "question": "A person who thinks quickly and finds smart solutions is...",
            "type": "multiple_choice"
        },
        {
            "answer": "Australian",
            "img_src": "",
            "question": "If a person is from Australia, their nationality is ...",
            "type": "short_answer"
        },
        {
            "answer": "Personality",
            "img_src": "",
            "question": "A personâ€™s behavior, attitude, and emotional traits define their ...",
            "type": "short_answer"
        },
        {
            "answer": "Friendly",
            "img_src": "",
            "question": "Someone who easily gets along with others and enjoys being around people is ...",
            "type": "short_answer"
        },
        {
            "answer": "American",
            "img_src": "",
            "question": "A person from America is called ...",
            "type": "short_answer"
        },
        {
            "answer": "Make friends",
            "img_src": "",
            "question": "If you introduce yourself to new people and build a good relationship, you ...",
            "type": "short_answer"
        },
        {
            "answer": "Malaysian",
            "img_src": "",
            "question": "A person from Malaysia has the nationality ...",
            "type": "short_answer"
        }
    ]
}